There's so much concerning
vaccines, but hey, I'm the guinea pig. I
got a vaccine in Colombia yesterday for
yellow fever. I had to get it to go back
to Costa Rica. And a lot of people are
telling me I'm going to die, I'm going
to have horrible side effects. But what
I'm going to do is go barefooted up the
most rugged mountain, Las Cruces, and
see how many pull-ups I can do on an
empty stomach after a 2 and 1/2 hour
hike in the hot sun. And I'm almost
voting. Let's see what this old man can
do. This is a absolutely punishing hike
up some of the most slipperiest rocky
level see. Hey Zach. When I said I
wanted to have fun, this is what I was
talking about. You knew exactly what I
wanted. Yeah, I'm looking out for it,
man.
>> There's three crosses at the top.
No Joe Fills will hike up a rugged
mountain barefoot to go kneel at a
cross. No lie, I checked it. What is
this? Gangster as hell. I got these
three crosses. You know, Jesus is in my
homeboy. And I also have calisthenics
parts, man. This appeals to the chain
gang in me, dog. Oh, you ain't been in
that chain gang, that ain't that
bad, dog.
>> I thought You'll get your wham whams and
zoom zooms, get you a honey bun. But I
got out of the chain gang. Get you a
pocket dog, get you over there with a
water bag.
>> And then I hooked around I know how
water feefee though. No, no, no, that
water bag, not no feefee. I went to
Colombia. Fly some spades, hit some
tongs. I feel like I'm back home. I love
Colombia this far, but still saying
[music] "Pura Vida."
Veinte cinco. I have 25. I got back at
the room, took a shower. I feel great. I
look great. I am great. You see it here.
No problem whatsoever. I'm not trying to
give you some propaganda, just a little
bit of truth. I took the shot, I went up
a mountain, I crushed some pull-ups,
feeling fine, no problems. And I love
Colombia. Still got a little chain gang
in me, too.